f30post.com 2018-12-25

# Privacy Policy

BIMMERPOST Privacy Notice  
Last Updated: May 18, 2018 

BIMMERPOST knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. **By visiting BIMMERPOST, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.**

The term BIMMERPOST refers to BIMMERPOST.com and all related domains referred to as "The Site" in our Terms of Service. 

**What Personal Information About Users Does BIMMERPOST Store?**

The information provided to BIMMERPOST is varied but limited in scope and is provided by you. 

  * **Information You Give Us** : With registration, we store the registered username, registered e-mail address, IP address, registered password, birthday, date of registration and subsequent dates of site visit, social media contact information. Your password is encoded in such a way that we cannot retrieve your raw password. This information is stored locally.
  * **E-mail** : Occasionally, when really big news comes across our desk, we will send out an e-mail to your registered address to inform you of this news. You have the option to opt-out of any emails sent from our website by selecting the option in our user control panel. _We do not under any circumstances sell, trade or otherwise give out e-mail addresses. No ifs ands or buts!_
  * You may see a comprehensive list of all the personal data being stored under your account at any time by visiting our Personal Data Portal

**User Generated Content, Online Communities and Forums, Profiles, Surveys, Reviews and Ratings**   
You may choose to publicly disclose personal information about yourself and others in the course of (i) contributing user generated content (for instance articles, blogs, surveys, reviews, ratings, or podcasts), (ii) communicating with others in our online forums, communities, or chat rooms, (iii) creating user profiles for public view, or (iv) posting images, photos, or videos. Be aware, information that you voluntarily disclose in any of these areas of our sites or services is unencrypted, public information and, therefore, there can be no expectation of privacy or confidentiality, except if the terms of use of the site or service specifically limit use of the content (for example, we may let you know how such survey and rating responses will be used and if anonymity is an option). Any personal information you submit in the course of interacting in these public activities can be read, collected, or used by other users. Prior to posting in these areas, we encourage you to read the specific site's or service's terms of use, as we are not responsible for the personal information you choose to make public in any of these areas and strongly recommend against sharing any personal health or other sensitive information that could directly or indirectly be traced to any individual, including yourself. 

**What About Cookies and other tracking technologies?**   
We or our third-party service providers may collect and store certain technical information when you use our sites and services. For example, our servers receive and automatically collect information about your computer and browser, including, for instance, your IP address, browser type, domain name from which you accessed the site or service, device size and other software or hardware information. If you access our sites and services from a mobile or other device, we may collect a unique device identifier assigned to that device (UDID), type of device, general GPS location, or other transactional information for that device in order to serve content to it and to improve your experience in using the sites or services. 

In addition, we or our third-party service providers may collect information about how you use of our sites, including but not limited to, the date and time you visit the sites, the areas or pages of the sites that you visit, the amount of time you spend viewing the sites, the number of times you return to the sites, visits to sites outside our network, preferred language, and other click-stream data. 

We or our third-party service providers may use cookies and other tracking technologies (including browser cookies, pixels, beacons, mobile application identifiers, and Adobe Flash technology) to help us recognize you across different sites and services, improve your experience, increase security, measure use and effectiveness of our services, and serve advertising. You can control cookies through your browser settings and other tools. For more information about our use of cookies, please read our Cookie Policy. 

By visiting our sites and services, you consent to the placement of cookies and beacons in your browser and HTML-based emails in accordance with this privacy policy and our Cookie Policy. 

You can opt-out of being targeted by certain third party advertising companies online by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative, Omniture, Aperture, PrivacyChoice, and/or Digital Advertising Alliance. 

We currently do not respond to "Do Not Track" browser signals. Accordingly, your navigation on our sites and services may be tracked as part of our efforts to gather user information described above. If you arrive at our sites and services by way of a link from a third-party site that does respond to â€œDo Not Trackâ€ browser signals, such â€œDo Not Trackâ€ browser signal recognition will end as soon as you reach our sites and services. 

**Does BIMMERPOST Share the Information It Receives?**   
Information security about our users is important to us, and we are not in the business of selling it to others. We do not share user information with anyone, with the following exceptions: 

_Protection of BIMMERPOST and Others_ : We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with law; enforce or apply our Terms and Conditions of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of BIMMERPOST, our users, or others. Obviously, however, this does not include selling, renting, sharing, or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information from customers for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Notice. 

_Business Transfers_ : As we continue to develop this site, we might sell services or business units. In such transactions, user information generally is transferred along with the rest of the service or business unit. Also, in the event that BIMMERPOST is acquired, user information will of course be included in the transaction. 

**Your Consent**   
Other than as set out above, you will always receive notice when information about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information. 

**What About Third-Party Advertisers?**   
Our site includes third-party advertising and links to other websites. We do not provide any personally identifiable customer information to these advertisers or third-party websites. 

These third-party websites and advertisers, or Internet advertising companies working on their behalf, sometimes use technology to send (or "serve") the advertisements that appear on our website directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use cookies, JavaScript, web beacons (also known as action tags or single-pixel gifs), and other technologies to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content (such as Google through the Google AdSense program). This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites). We do not have access to or control over cookies or other features that they may use, and the information practices of these advertisers and third-party websites are not covered by this Privacy Notice. Please contact them directly for more information about their privacy practices. In addition, the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) offers useful information about Internet advertising companies (also called "ad networks" or "network advertisers"), including information about how to opt-out of their information collection. 

**How Secure Is Information About Me?**   
We work to protect the security of your registration information on our servers and encrypt your passwords with the strictest algorithms. 

It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer. 

**What Choices and Access Do I Have?**   
You can always choose not to provide information, even though it might be needed to particapte in the forum discussion. 

You can add or update certain information, such as your e-mail address, by using our User Administration pages. If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please use our User Administration pages to adjust your preferences. The "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. Additionally, you can disable or delete similar data used by browser add-ons, such as Flash cookies, by changing the add-on's settings or visiting the Web site of its manufacturer. However, because cookies allow you to take advantage of some of BIMMERPOST's essential features, we recommend that you leave them turned on. 

**Children**   
BIMMERPOST is not intended for use by children under the legal driving age in your state or country of residence. If you are under this age, you may not submit information about yourself to BIMMERPOST. 

**International Users**   
We are headquartered in the United States. Our sites and services are hosted and administrated in the United States or hosted with cloud service providers who are headquartered in the United States and are intended for users in the United States. If you are located outside the United States, be aware that information you provide to us or that we obtain as a result of your use of our sites and services may be processed in, transferred to, and stored in the United States and will be subject to United States law. The privacy and data protection laws of the United States may be different from the laws of your country of residence.   
By using our sites and services or providing us with your information, you consent to the transfer of your information to the United States for processing and storage. 

**California Privacy Rights**   
FOR RESIDENTS OF CALIFORNIA ONLY. Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code requires select businesses to disclose policies relating to the sharing of certain categories of your personal information with third parties. If you reside in California and you have provided us with your personal information, you may request information about our disclosures of certain categories of your personal information to third parties for direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please email bimmerpost.com@gmail.com with "California Privacy Rights" in the subject line and allow 30 days for a response. We will not accept requests via the telephone, mail, or by facsimile, and we are not responsible for notices that are not labeled or sent properly, or that do not have complete information. 

FOR RESIDENTS OF CALIFORNIA UNDER THE AGE OF 18. In accordance with Section 22581 of the California Business and Professions Code, you may request and obtain the removal of content or information you have publicly posted. To make such a request, please email bimmerpost.com@gmail.com with the Subject or Title line "California Privacy Rights" in the subject line. Please specify the site(s) or service(s) to which your removal request relates, including any URLs where the content or information is posted, and the specific content or information you posted for which you are requesting removal. Please be aware that such a request does not ensure complete or comprehensive removal of the content or information you have posted and that there may be circumstances in which the law does not require or allow removal even if requested. 

**EU Privacy Rights**   
FOR RESIDENTS OF THE EUROPEAN UNION ONLY. Under European data protection law, in certain circumstances, you have the right to: 

request access to your personal information;  
request correction of your personal information;  
request erasure of your personal information;  
object to processing of your personal information;  
request restriction of processing your personal information;  
request transfer of your personal information; and  
withdraw your consent.

In addition, you have the right to ask us not to process your personal information for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your personal information) if we intend to use your personal information for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. 

You can exercise any of these rights by filling out our Privacy Contact Form or sending an email to bimmerpost.com@gmail.com with "EU Privacy Rights" in the subject line. If you believe that we have not complied with its obligations under this Privacy Policy or European law, you have the right to make a complaint to an EU Data Protection Authority. 

**Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions**   
If you choose to visit BIMMERPOST, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Terms of Services, including limitations on damages, resolution of disputes, and application of the law of the state of New York. If you have any concern about privacy at BIMMERPOST, please send us a thorough description via our Contact Us button at the bottom of our forums pages, and we will try to resolve it. Our business changes constantly. This Notice and the Terms of Service will change also, and use of information that we gather now is subject to the Privacy Notice in effect at the time of use. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, but you should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Notice applies to all information that we have about you and your account. We stand behind the promises we make, however, and will never materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of customer information collected in the past without the consent of affected customers.
